https://www.amronintl.com/privacy_policy

Loading...
Continue shopping
Language:
Currency:
Allied Witan
AlphaTec (Trellchem)
ContiTech
Cortland (Fibron)
Medline
Microflex (Ansell)
CONTACT US
Get immediate service.
Call Us
(877) 462-6700
(760) 208-6500
Don't want to call?
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and make use of personal information. By visiting this site you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Before using this site, please review the Amron Site Terms. We do not rent or sell your personal information to third parties.
Amron International may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and
it will become effective when posted. You agree to review this Privacy Policy periodically to be aware of any changes. Your continued use of this site after any changes to the Privacy Policy are posted will be considered acceptance of
those changes. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can
always contact Amron International customer support by email sales@amronintl.com or toll
free (877) 462-6700 Monday – Friday 8am-5pm PST. You can also write to us at:
Amron International - 1380 Aspen Way Vista, CA 92081
Personal Information
We collect personal information you provide to us by lawful and fair means. For example, we collect information when you create an account, sign up for email promotions, request a quote, contact us, use the interactive areas and features on our site, make a purchase, and when you email, call, or otherwise communicate with us. We may also collect your email address if you provide it when completing a survey, a product review or entering an online contest. The types of personal information we collect include, name, address, phone and/or fax number, email address, photo, and account information (e.g. online registration information). Our website checkout page is compliant with the guidelines set by the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS). Cardholder information is not stored, processed or transmitted on Amron’s website or its servers. Cardholder information includes credit card number, debit card number, expiration date,
CVV and PIN. Amron utilizes Control Scan and PayPal which are third party PCI Compliant payment applications that transmit cardholder information. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.
Data Security, Integrity and Retention
The security, integrity and confidentiality of your information are extremely important to us. We have implemented technical, administrative and physical security measures that are designed to protect customer information from unauthorized access, disclosure, use and modification. From time to time, we review our security procedures to consider appropriate new technology and methods. Please be aware though that, despite our best efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We will retain your personal information for the length of time needed to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.
Cookies and Other Information Collected
This site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the
features offered. A "cookie" is a small data file that our sites
transfer to your computer. We deliver these cookies and collect data on our
sites, and we may also use a third party agent to deliver cookies and collect
data. We can automatically collect data using cookies. For example, when your
web browser accesses our site, we obtain certain types of information, such as
your IP address, the type of browser you use, access times, and the page you visited
before visiting our site. We may also collect information about your computer's
operating system and information about your usage and activity on our site.
Cookies can also help us customize and improve our site for visitors. If
you desire, the “help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you
how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser
notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.
Our Use of Personal Information
We use the personal information we collect about you for a variety of purposes, for example, to:
provide and deliver products and services, process and complete transactions and send you related information, including order status, order confirmations, tracking information, invoices, updates, recall notices and support and administrative messages;
respond to your comments, requests and questions and to provide customer service;
send you communications about Amron International and our partners products, services, offers, promotions and news;
maintain and administer your www.amronintl.com online account;
operate and improve our site and services.
Sharing of Personal Information
We may share personal information about you outside of Amron International and its affiliates, including as follows:
We may share personal information with third parties who perform important tasks such as processing credit card transactions and performing web maintenance services on our behalf. We require that our vendors maintain confidentiality of any information about our customers that may be disclosed to them and to use such information solely for the purpose of providing the services on Amron’s behalf.
We may also post or publish your information when you submit comments, stories, photos, and videos in connection with other areas of our site.
Personal information may be shared as part of a corporate business transaction, such as a merger or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company, joint venture, corporate reorganization, financing or sale of company assets. It may also be shared in the event of insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personal information could be transferred to third parties as one of the business assets in the transaction.
We may share personal information (i) to comply with laws or to respond to lawful requests and legal process, (ii) to protect the rights and property of Amron International, our agents, members, and others, including to enforce our agreements, policies, and terms of use, or (iii) in an emergency to protect the personal safety of Amron International, our members, our customers, or any other person.
Third-Party Advertising Partners
We use third-party service providers, including Google, to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet.
These advertising service providers may collect non-identifiable information about your visits to our website, and your interactions with our products and services. Such non-identifiable information does not include your name, address, email address or other personal information. The information is collected through the use of cookies and pixel tags (also known as action tags), which is industry-standard technology used by most major websites.
If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices for not having this information used by third-party service providers, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/what-are-my-options
You may opt out of
Google's use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page:  http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/
Unsubscribe option
You may opt out of receiving promotional emails from Amron International at any time, please use our unsubscribe link found at the bottom of our promotional email or if you prefer contact us by phone, toll-free at (877) 462-6700 or (760) 208-6500, Monday – Friday 8am – 5pm PST. You may also email your request to sales@amronintl.com with subject line 'Opt Out'. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as emails about your orders, account and ongoing business relations.
Security of Personal Information
Amron International will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. Amron International is committed to conducting business in accordance with this Privacy Policy in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
MKT-POL-001 REV 2.0
Release Date October 9, 2018
Timeline & History
Careers
Terms & Conditions
Site Terms
Privacy Policy
Shipping Information
Get immediate service. Call an Amron Representative Today!Domestic U.S.: (877) 462-6700 International: (760) 208-6500
What do you think of our website?
Give us feedback
© 2005-2020 - Copyright Amron International, Inc. All Rights Reserved
video title
video content
